[music]
>> When you go to a party, you eat.
>> [music]
>> So, what I like about this building also
by yes to me. I got a new kitchen. I
think that's the meeting place also for
all the people here and because you can
get that in your garden and all the
people going to the rooftop also.
Everyone would pass by the kitchen.
That's why
oh, that's something different then.
Yeah,
you better tell your identity of Mira
Nila.
Yeah, we decided to stay
and [music] choose this place for our
birthday celebration.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah.
>> Not that hot also.
>> Super nice here. Super relaxing then.
So, we hope now our friends would
actually enjoy the the celebration.
Because that's what we really want for
relaxing on a weekend.
I'm going to view.
>> [music]
>> I don't know one word to define
something like don't know one word to
define
like me or whatever.
>> Um
You know tell me that
her father
>> [laughter]
>> leader
>> two words
>> [music]
>> role model
>> passionate
>> encore [laughter]
>> tough
>> timeless
>> self-made
>> Eliza is
>> reliable
>> Eliza is genuine.
>> kind-hearted
>> [music]
>> iconic
>> Look at my [music] teammates.
>> Of course.
>> They're going to start eating
>> right away.
>> That's how you do it, guys. When you go
to a party, when you go to a party,
you eat.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> I just want to say thank you to everyone
that's [music] here. Thank you everyone.
I know everybody's busy.
We're just happy that everyone's here
and
we love you guys so much.
>> Thank you so much for spending [music]
your afternoon
with us. And
So happy happy birthday to you and to
all his friends
for making [music] time today and let's
celebrate Ian's birthday. Yay!
>> [music and singing]
[music]
[cheering]
>> Um I just really want to wish you a
happy birthday and I'm so lucky and so
blessed to have a partner like you who's
been supportive and understands and
loves me
just by who I am. So I'm I'm so
grateful. I'm so happy and I'm I'm so
excited to spend the next 50 years with
you. [music] I love you, babe.
>> My message to Ian would be well, first
of all, happy happy birthday. I hope you
had fun today. Well, first
would be uh
I just wish
you genuine happiness.
>> [music]
>> I really pray now my heart will be in
genuine happiness. Second one would be I
really do hope now
you can spend more time for yourself.
And lastly you go uh
but I really health.
And dreams
birthday.